<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ameer Taweel</title><link>https://ameertaweel.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Ameer Taweel</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 15:10:22 +0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ameertaweel.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>SARS CoV 2 Interactome 3D</title><link>https://ameertaweel.github.io/projects/sars-cov-2-interactome-3d/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 15:10:22 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://ameertaweel.github.io/projects/sars-cov-2-interactome-3d/</guid><description>This project is a web-based server for navigating and visualizing possible interactions between SARS-CoV-2 (the virus that causes COVID-19) and human host proteins.
I gained valuable experience working on this project, as this is my first time contributing to scientific research. I was responsible for building the serverside API and the client webpage. I developed the API using PHP and the webpage using both JavaScript and PHP.
I also learned a lot about the research topic itself, working with a team, and the process of doing scientific research.</description></item><item><title>Blockchain Specialization</title><link>https://ameertaweel.github.io/certificates/blockchain/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2022 15:16:56 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://ameertaweel.github.io/certificates/blockchain/</guid><description>I started taking the Blockchain Specialization offered by University at Buffalo on Coursera. The specialization consists of four courses:
Blockchain Basics Smart Contracts Decentralized Applications (Dapps) Blockchain Platforms I have completed the first course so far (View Certificate) and started taking the second one.</description></item><item><title>NixOS Contributions</title><link>https://ameertaweel.github.io/projects/nixos/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 22:23:51 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://ameertaweel.github.io/projects/nixos/</guid><description>I started using NixOS as my primary operating system in late 2021. As I was migrating my dotfiles for NixOS, some packages I wanted to use were missing from the NixOS package collection, Nixpkgs. Therefore, I contributed the following package definitions to Nixpkgs:
d0c-s4vage/lookatme: An interactive, terminal-based markdown presenter.
View Pull Request sindrets/winshift.nvim: Rearrange Neovim windows with ease.
View Pull Request skywind3000/asyncrun.vim: Run async tasks in Vim/NeoVim and output to quickfix list.</description></item></channel></rss>