<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Certificates on Ameer Taweel</title><link>https://ameertaweel.github.io/certificates/</link><description>Recent content in Certificates on Ameer Taweel</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Jul 2022 16:22:53 +0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ameertaweel.github.io/certificates/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Deep Learning Specialization</title><link>https://ameertaweel.github.io/certificates/deep-learning/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Jul 2022 16:22:53 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://ameertaweel.github.io/certificates/deep-learning/</guid><description>I started taking the Deep Learning Specialization offered by DeepLearnin.AI on Coursera. The specialization consists of five courses:
Neural Networks and Deep Learning Improving Deep Neural Networks: Hyperparameter Tuning, Regularization and Optimization Structuring Machine Learning Projects Convolutional Neural Networks Sequence Models I have completed the first course of the specialization successfully:
View Course 1 Certificate I started taking the second course of the specialization.</description></item><item><title>Game Development With Unity3D</title><link>https://ameertaweel.github.io/certificates/unity-game-dev/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 00:00:52 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://ameertaweel.github.io/certificates/unity-game-dev/</guid><description>I started taking the Game Development With Unity3D Specialization offered by Michigan State University on Coursera. The specialization consists of five courses:
Build a 2D Shooter Build a 2D Platformer Build a 3D Shooter Build a 3D Platformer Captsone Project I have completed the first two course so far:
View Course 1 Certificate View Course 2 Certificate I started taking the third course.</description></item><item><title>Blockchain Specialization</title><link>https://ameertaweel.github.io/certificates/blockchain/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2022 15:16:56 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://ameertaweel.github.io/certificates/blockchain/</guid><description>I started taking the Blockchain Specialization offered by University at Buffalo on Coursera. The specialization consists of four courses:
Blockchain Basics Smart Contracts Decentralized Applications (Dapps) Blockchain Platforms I have completed all the four courses of the specialization successfully.
View Course 1 Certificate View Course 2 Certificate View Course 3 Certificate View Course 4 Certificate Also, you can view the specialization&amp;rsquo;s certificate here.</description></item></channel></rss>